Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Battle in Seattle disc 5, 2006- (Box-folder 43-54)
- Soccer, 2006- (Box-folder 43-55)
- Volleyball vs. Western, 2006- (Box-folder 43-56)
- Provost Dave Soltz, 2004- (Box-folder 43-57)
- James Nimicht ,C.O.B. Professor, 2004- (Box-folder 43-58)
- Football/ Soccer, Volleyball Portraits, 2007- (Box-folder 43-59)
- XC Headshots, 2007- (Box-folder 43-60)
- Football Media Day, 2007- (Box-folder 43-61)
- Baseball Group, Softball Action, 2007- (Box-folder 43-62)
- Baseball, Softball Mugs, 11/2007 Men's and Women's Basketball, 2008- (Box-folder 43-63)
- Soccer, Basketball Mugs, 2007- (Box-folder 43-64)
- Volleyball Heads, 2002- (Box-folder 43-65)
- Men's Basketball, 2007 Spring Mugs, Beau Baldwin H.S. Press Conference (Box-folder 43-66)
- Fall Mugs/Teams, Football, Soccer. Volleyball, 2008- (Box-folder 43-67)
- Baseball/Softball, Basketball Game, Softball Game, Holtman and Wallace, TV Shoot/Interview, 2008- (Box-folder 43-68)
- Sports: Baseball, baseball headshots, Men's Basketball Team, Softball headshots, Track Team, 2009 Women's Basketball, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 43-69)
- Sports Volleyball 10/2009, Softball 04/2010, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 43-70)
- Baseball 04/2010, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 43-71)
- Men's and Women's Basketball 1/2010, Pink Zone Uniforms with Basketball, 04/2010 Rugby, 10/2009 Volleyball, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 43-72)
- Sports Disc 2: 04/2010 Rugby, 09/2010 Soccer (Box-folder 43-73)
- Sports Disc 1: 04/2010 Baseball, 01/2010 Basketball, 11/2010 Men's Basketball, 02/2010 Pink Zone With Basketball Seniors (Box-folder 43-74)
- Sport Picks, 04/2010 Spike Arlt, 09/2010 Volleyball, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 43-75)
- Baseball, Softball, 2009- (Box-folder 43-76)
- Sports, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 43-77)
- Sports Football, Men's and Women's Basketball, Soccer, Sport Extractions Volleyball, 2009- (Box-folder 43-78)
- Spike Arlt Invite, Baseball, SURC Spinner Bikes, 2007- (Box-folder 43-79)
- Homecoming Football, 2011- (Box-folder 43-80)
- Homecoming Football Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 43-81)
- Softball, 2011- (Box-folder 43-82)
- Spring Sports: Spike Arlt Track Meet, Baseball, 2011- (Box-folder 43-83)
- Volleyball: CWU vs AAU, Green Scarf PS Work, 2011- (Box-folder 43-84)
- Sports: Men's Basketball Dunks, 04/2010 Softball, 09/2010 Volleyball, 01/2011 Wellington and Fans, 01/2011 Women's Basketball, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 43-85)
- "Waters" Project Photo by Ian Quitadamo, 2008- (Box-folder 43-86)
- Football Practice Wildcat Cup Freshman N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 43-87)
- Football Team Coaches, 2002- (Box-folder 43-88)
- Basketball Men's, 03/2004 Football (Box-folder 43-89)
- Variety: 2003 Girls’ Basketball Team, 2003 Soccer, 2003 Swimming, 2003 Track, 2003 Volleyball, 02/2003 Snow, 2004 Music Construction, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 43-90)
- Volleyball Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-91)
- Volleyball Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-92)
- Rugby Practice, Intermural Flag Football, 2004- (Box-folder 43-93)
- Women's Basketball, 2004- (Box-folder 43-94)
- Women's Basketball, 2004- (Box-folder 43-95)
- Men's and Women's Basketball, 2005- (Box-folder 43-96)
- Volleyball, 2005- (Box-folder 43-97)
- Soccer, 2005- (Box-folder 43-98)
- Football Practice, Homecoming Football, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 43-99)
- Men's Basketball Mugs, 2006- (Box-folder 43-100)
- Basketball Portraits Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-101)
- Basketball Portraits Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-102)
- Men's and Women's Basketball, Miscellaneous Sport Picks, 2006- (Box-folder 43-103)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-104)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-105)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 3, 2006- (Box-folder 43-106)
- Football, 2007- (Box-folder 43-107)
- Volleyball, 2007- (Box-folder 43-108)
- Urinetown Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 43-109)
- Theater Arts: Spaces Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-110)
- Theater Arts: Spaces Disc 2, 2006- (Box-folder 43-111)
- Don Quixote, 2008- (Box-folder 43-112)
- Red Curtain Review N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 43-113)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 43-114)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 43-115)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 43-116)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 43-117)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 43-118)
- Charlotte's Web Disc 2, 2010- (Box-folder 43-119)
- Theatre Variety Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 43-120)
- Darwin Bellah Soltz, 2005- (Box-folder 43-121)
- Foreigner Disc 1 2005 (Box-folder 43-122)
- Foreigner Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 43-123)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up REH Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 43-124)
- Disc 14 Open Spaces Winnebago Pt. 3 Green Side, 2002- (Box-folder 43-125)
- Stock Disc 15 Open Spaces Winnebago Part 4 Cleaned Photos, 2002- (Box-folder 43-126)
- Campus Flowers, no date- (Box-folder 43-127)
- Studio Flowers, no date- (Box-folder 43-128)
- Viewbook Pages 7,8, and 15, no date- (Box-folder 43-129)
- View book Pages 11,13, no date- (Box-folder 43-130)
- Stock Disc 3: CHCI, Lynnwood, police, Speakers, 9/11-2002, Trustees, Region (Box-folder 43-131)
- Snow disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 43-132)
- President's Report, 2002- (Box-folder 43-133)
- Stock Disc 2: Conceptual, 2002- (Box-folder 43-134)
- Conceptual 2, 2003- (Box-folder 43-135)
- Yakima Continuing Education, 2003- (Box-folder 43-136)
- Conceptual 1, 2003- (Box-folder 43-137)
- Franken-Glass 4, no date- (Box-folder 43-138)
- RHA Group 3 Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-139)
- Lynn Brewer C.O.B. Speaker, 2004- (Box-folder 43-140)
- Disc 2 James Ray 23-106, 2004- (Box-folder 43-141)
- Disc 1 James Ray 1-22, 2004- (Box-folder 43-142)
- Disc 3 James Ray 106-168, 2004- (Box-folder 43-143)
- UrineTown Disc 1, 2010- (Box-folder 43-144)
- Barto Hall Grand Opening, 2012- (Box-folder 43-145)
- Muzzall Demolition Last Piece (Wing) -Disc 1, 2008- (Box-folder 43-146)
- Muzzall Demolition Last Wing, 2008- (Box-folder 43-147)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-148)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-149)
- Muzzall/Courson Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-150)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-151)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-152)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-153)
- Courson/Muzzall Demolition, 2008- (Box-folder 43-154)
- Images Courson, 2008- (Box-folder 43-155)
- Dean Hall Renovation, Fall Energy Shots, Fishbowl Study N.S., Football Readers, IET Toy Production, Mariachi Los Comparos, 2008- (Box-folder 43-156)
- Fall Miscellaneous; Malls, Brooklane, Getz/Short, Student Village, Dean Hall Construction, 2008- (Box-folder 43-157)
- Fall Campus: Malls, Colors, Movement, Res/Hall Construction, 2008- (Box-folder 43-158)
- Miscellaneous: Christmas Gifts in President's Office, Fashion Show N.S., Holiday Reception N.S., Job Fair, 2008- (Box-folder 43-159)
- Miscellaneous Events: SURC and Students N.S., Frisbee N.S., Roadtrip Nation N.S., Salsa Lessons N.S., X-Mas N.S., Yakama Speelyii N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 43-160)
- SURC Students: Juggler Guy N.S., 2008- (Box-folder 43-161)
- Softball, 2006- (Box-folder 43-162)
- Football Mugs, 2006- (Box-folder 43-163)
- Soccer, Volleyball, Jonathan Gordon Mugs, 2006- (Box-folder 43-164)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 43-165)
- Battle in Seattle Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 43-166)
- Football Practice, 2007- (Box-folder 43-167)
- Stock Disc 4 Nature Details, ROTC, Headshots Gen. Political, McIntyre, Baker, Schliep, Soltz, 2002- (Box-folder 43-168)
- Stock Disc 5 Housing Staff/Group, Cantwell, Corona, Doc Hastings, 2002- (Box-folder 43-169)
- Stock Disc 11: commencement, Seattle Stock Part 2, Student Life Part 1, 2002- (Box-folder 43-170)
- Stock Disc 12: Student Life Part 2, Open Spaces Winnebago Part 1, 2002- (Box-folder 43-171)
- Stock Disc 9: Barge, Black, Bouillon, General Campus, Hebeler, Holmes, Lind, Nicholson, Shaw, 2002- (Box-folder 43-172)
- Viewbook Images Covers and Pages 1-5, no date- (Box-folder 43-173)
- Viewbook 4, no date- (Box-folder 43-174)
- Stock Disc 10: 2002 sports, Seattle Stock Pt. 1 (Box-folder 43-175)
- Stock Disc 8: International Ad, International Students, Farrell, Garden, Science, 2002- (Box-folder 43-176)
- Stock Disc 7: C.A.M.P., Aerial Shots, 2002- (Box-folder 43-177)
- Stock Disc 1: Infrared, Theater, Wellington, 2002- (Box-folder 43-178)
- Seattle Stock, 2002- (Box-folder 43-179)
- Stock Disc 6: Miller, 2002 President Rapport Image, Black and White Housing Poster (Box-folder 43-180)
- Stock Disc 13: Open Spaces Winnebago Part 2, 2002- (Box-folder 43-181)
- Scrooge (Stage Shots) Stop Kiss Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 43-182)
- Scrooge Disc 1 Actors, 2009- (Box-folder 43-183)
- Stop Kiss Disc 3, 2009- (Box-folder 43-184)
- Miscellaneous Portraits Camp 214, Cubilie, Anne; Denison, Christine; Pederson, Lene; Philosophy Faculty: Rable, Tricia; Shoemaker, Ian; Sterkel, Kendra, 2013-2014 (Box-folder 43-185)
- How I Learned to Drive Disc 4, 2004- (Box-folder 43-186)
- How I Learned to Drive Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 43-187)
- How I Learned to Drive Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-188)
- Foreigner Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 43-189)
- Theater Workshops Disc 1, 2005- (Box-folder 43-190)
- Theater Workshops Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 43-191)
- Theater Workshops Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 43-192)
- Theater Workshops Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 43-193)
- Theater Workshops Disc 5, 2005- (Box-folder 43-194)
- Theater Workshops Disc 6, 2005- (Box-folder 43-195)
- How I learned to Drive Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-196)
- Lloyd's Prayer Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-197)
- Lloyd's Prayer Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-198)
- Bus Stop 1-100 Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-199)
- Bus Stop 106-200 Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-200)
- Bus Stop 201-289 Disc 3, 2004- (Box-folder 43-201)
- Two Gentleman from Verona, 2008- (Box-folder 43-202)
- Mama Tomcat's Flying School Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 43-203)
- Mama Tomcat's Flying School Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 43-204)
- West Side Story, 2003- (Box-folder 43-205)
- Pinocchio, 2003- (Box-folder 43-206)
- Bird Woman Disc 1, 2004- (Box-folder 43-207)
- Bird Woman Disc 2, 2004- (Box-folder 43-208)
- 7 Brides For 7 Brothers, 2009- (Box-folder 43-209)
- Construction: Lombard, S.U.B. Recreation, 2005- (Box-folder 43-210)
- Construction: S.U.B. Recreation Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 43-211)
- Construction Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 43-212)
- Construction Disc 4, 2005- (Box-folder 43-213)
- Aerials Looking East Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-214)
- Aerials Looking East Disc 1, 2006- (Box-folder 43-215)
- Music Building, 2004- (Box-folder 43-216)
- Fall Music Building: Science Building, Interior Stair with Students, 2004- (Box-folder 43-217)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H. Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 43-218)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H. Disc 2, 2007- (Box-folder 43-219)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H. Disc 3, 2007- (Box-folder 43-220)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H./Wides Cast and Crew, 2007- (Box-folder 43-221)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H. Disc 5, 2007- (Box-folder 43-222)
- Christmas Carol Pick Up R.E.H. Disc 6, 2007- (Box-folder 43-223)
- A Christmas Carol Disc 1, 2007- (Box-folder 43-224)
- Frankenstein Disc 2, 2005- (Box-folder 43-225)
- Frankenstein Disc 3, 2005- (Box-folder 43-226)
- Importance of Being Earnest, 2007- (Box-folder 43-227)
- Orchesis, 2007- (Box-folder 43-228)
- NOH Telling, Ailey 2, 2007- (Box-folder 43-229)
- Vietnam 101, 2007- (Box-folder 43-230)
- CWU Buildings Disc 1 Al-Monty, Anderson, Moore, Bassettis, Brooklane, Brooks Library, Button Hall, Campus Court, Carmody, Computer Center, Farrell, 2006- (Box-folder 43-231)
- CWU Buildings Disc 2: flight Tech, Getz/Short, Green Hall, Health Center, Hogue, International Center, Jongward, Munson, Muzzall, North Hall, Old Heat, 2006- (Box-folder 43-232)
- A Christmas Carol: Photo Call Actor Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 43-233)
- Music McConnell Twilight Shots R.V. and N.S., no date- (Box-folder 43-234)
- CWU Snow Barge/ McConnell, Campus/Science, Ice Leaves, 2006- (Box-folder 43-235)
- Craig's Hill Panoramic, 2006- (Box-folder 43-236)
- Spring Campus DVD, 2006- (Box-folder 43-237)
- Still Life with Iris Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 43-238)
- Still Life with Iris Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 43-239)
- Distinguished Professors Disc 2, 1977-2013 (Box-folder 43-240)
- Distinguished Professors Disc 3, 1977-2013 (Box-folder 43-241)
- Brown, Greg: CWU Alumni, Principal, Mt. Baker Middle School, 2013- (Box-folder 43-242)
- COB Profs Teaching; Sipic, Toni; Tenerelli, Thomas, 2013- (Box-folder 43-243)
- COB Profs Teaching: Wilson, Theresa; Wu, Coco, 2013- (Box-folder 43-244)
- CWU Police Group/Individual, 2013- (Box-folder 43-245)
- Spring Athletic Hall of Fame, 2014- (Box-folder 43-246)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend: BBQ, BI-Mart Night, Bite of the Burg, Convocation, Movers and Shakers, Welcome in Nicholson Pavilion, Wildcat Cup, 2014- (Box-folder 43-247)
- April ASL 414, 2014- (Box-folder 43-248)
- Avey, James; Bailey, Bill; COB Dean's Council; COB Faculty Group, 2013- (Box-folder 43-249)
- Fall Miscellaneous Portraits: Accounting Group, Career Services Linked in Headshots, Conner, Ralph; Darda, Dave; Deptula, Bryan; Ehoff, Clemense; Hendrickson, Bob; Kurtz, Martha; Moon, Mike; Mukherjee, Sayantani; Provost Council; Wyman, Tinja; Yastechnko, Alena; Studenka, Chris, 2013- (Box-folder 43-250)
- Fall Miscellaneous Portraits: Bakeman, Nancy; Boersma, Stuart; Cardenas, Ruben; Chavez, Kathryn; Chen, So Phourng, CLCE Group, Damm, Sharon; Elser/Seraile/Bafford Alumni Awards; Herman, Dan; Hernandez, Jill; Hitchcock, Kim; Hunt, Cindy; Kinnan, Sheri; Mohamed, Saeed; Nimnicht, James; Piacsek, Andy; Poe, Greg, 2013- (Box-folder 43-251)
- Fall Christmas, 2013- (Box-folder 43-252)
- Pecos Bill and the Ghost Stampede, 2007- (Box-folder 43-253)
- Secret Garden, 2010- (Box-folder 43-254)
- Snow Queen, 2011- (Box-folder 43-255)
- The Country Wife, 2011- (Box-folder 43-256)
- Reigen, 2011- (Box-folder 43-257)
- CTE A Christmas Carol Disc 1, 2011- (Box-folder 43-258)
- CTE A Christmas Carol Disc 2, 2011- (Box-folder 43-259)
- Theater Arts: RASA boxes Workshops, 2011- (Box-folder 43-260)
- Little Women, 2012- (Box-folder 43-261)
- May Kroll Todd chemistry Lab 314, 2014- (Box-folder 43-262)
- June Archaeology 614, 2014- (Box-folder 43-263)
- January Science Student Teaching, 2014- (Box-folder 43-264)
- Challenger, 2013- (Box-folder 43-265)
- Portraits: HS Band Camp group, Career Services Group, Cawley- Crane, Joan; Dorsey, Lindsey; Haldane, Dennis; Hercules, Brian; HR Staff Work Portraits, Orchesis heads, 2013- (Box-folder 43-266)
- Miscellaneous Portraits Anderson, Kari; COB Dean's council; Dudley Jason; EQUU Club at Orion 12/2013; Hilleman, Joanne 02/2014; Hudson, Joshua; Santiago, Sharlyn 1/2014, 2013-2014 (Box-folder 43-267)
- Larry Gookin Wind Ensemble, 2014- (Box-folder 43-268)
- Larry Gookin Wind Ensemble disc 2, 2014- (Box-folder 43-269)
- Trio welcome pow Wow, 2014- (Box-folder 43-270)
- DonDJFlowCyto, 2014- (Box-folder 43-271)
- CommStudent Agency 414, 2014- (Box-folder 43-272)
- Boots and Cats Rehearsal, 2014- (Box-folder 43-273)
- COB sports Marketing 414 mariners, 2014- (Box-folder 43-274)
- Gee David 5/14, 2014- (Box-folder 43-275)
- Spring Fabryllevente Students chem 414, 2014- (Box-folder 43-276)
- Ellensburg Commencement, 2014- (Box-folder 43-277)
- Camp CW-OO, 2014- (Box-folder 43-278)
- Spring Career Quest 5/14, 2014- (Box-folder 43-279)
- Comm/Sci RV, 2014- (Box-folder 43-280)
- Comm Studio/ Classroom 414, 2014- (Box-folder 43-281)
- Biology shots Audrey Huerta, 2014- (Box-folder 43-282)
- Distinguished professors Disc 1, no date- (Box-folder 43-283)
- Distinguished professors Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 43-284)
- Distinguished professors Disc 3, no date- (Box-folder 43-285)
- Provazhik Class utopia, no date- (Box-folder 43-286)
- Retiree Portraits: 1-B/W 5x7 of each file, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 44-1)
- Miscellaneous Portraits development Staff, Jay Forsyth, student Speakers Comm. Lunch Prints, Track Team, 2007- (Box-folder 44-2)
- Recreation Kayaks, 2007- (Box-folder 44-3)
- Orchestral Student Conductors, 2007- (Box-folder 44-4)
- Westside: Danice Feller, Heidi Fosse, Norm Gierlasinsky, Earl Overstreet, Carol Sullivan, 2007- (Box-folder 44-5)
- C.O.B. Students Group Portraits, DHC Students in Class, Wildcat Shop Staff Portraits, 2007- (Box-folder 44-6)
- Kairos Quartet, 2007- (Box-folder 44-7)
- Brass faculty Quintet, 2007- (Box-folder 44-8)
- Civic Engagement: Portraits and S.T.E.P. Shots, no date- (Box-folder 44-9)
- Career Services Portraits, Captures and P.S., 2007- (Box-folder 44-10)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Sarah Britto, Chamber choir, Heacock, G; Kleck, Judith; Krueger, Frederick Archives Unveil; Neighbors, Rebecca; Rawlinson; Wassell, Chad, 2007- (Box-folder 44-11)
- Housing Group Portraits, 2007- (Box-folder 44-12)
- Baldwin Houser, 2007- (Box-folder 44-13)
- CWU Orchestra Portrait, 2007- (Box-folder 44-14)
- Orchestra, 2007- (Box-folder 44-15)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Easlick, A.; Zakel-Larson, K.; Loveless, N.; Sousa-Wynn, C.; Szpek, H., 2007- (Box-folder 44-16)
- Portraits: Kleck, Judith, 2007- (Box-folder 44-17)
- Easton, Carrie; Herrera, Rosario; Savcier, Lisa; Backlund, Phil and Judy; Badgely, Margaret, 2007- (Box-folder 44-18)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Colson, Sandy; Corona, Rich; Student Circle Shots, Thompson, Stuart; Valdez, David; Villiers, Eric; Wellock, Tom, 2007- (Box-folder 44-19)
- Miscellaneous People: Armstrong, J.; Dr. Bentley, Bach, Glenn; Mayer, E.; Peiscl, T.; Pellet, T.; Stevens, T., 2007- (Box-folder 44-20)
- Bryson, Elizabeth; Jefferies, Stephen; Percussion Ensemble, 2007- (Box-folder 44-21)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Bicchieri, K.; Carpenter, v.; Coleman, GE.; Elementary Kids @CWU; Lee, M.; Solar Car Crew; Stacy, G.; Thomson, K.; Student Portraits in Studio, 2007- (Box-folder 44-22)
- Cheer Squad, 2007- (Box-folder 44-23)
- Fun Student Portraits and Groups, 2007- (Box-folder 44-24)
- Central theater Ensemble Studio Portraits, 2007- (Box-folder 44-25)
- Orchestra Rehersal: Student Conductors CAOIE, 2007- (Box-folder 44-26)
- CWU Spirit Group Shot, 2007- (Box-folder 44-27)
- Student Portraits, 2007- (Box-folder 44-28)
- Amy Horton-Costco Executive Speaks to Rex Moody's Class, 2007- (Box-folder 44-29)
- Portraits Bicchieri, K.; Bryne, S.; Coleman, G.E.; Stacy, G.; Goodey, Darwin. Lee, M., 2007- (Box-folder 44-30)
- Nate's Artwork and Jazz, 2008- (Box-folder 44-31)
- Fitch/Plourde, Class/Brooke, 2008- (Box-folder 44-32)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Becker, M.; Black, K; Dining Employees, General James Mattis; Gries, Peter; McGowan, M; Morgan, M.; Rham, Carmen; Spurgeon, Sarah; Wain-Coon, David, Student Health and Wellness Shots, 2007- (Box-folder 44-33)
- Miscellaneous Shots: Anderson Room, Mardi Gras Dinner Senior 65+/ Student Shots Meaningful Connections, Shaw-Smyser Entry, Wild Horse wind Farm, 2008- (Box-folder 44-34)
- Student Village Kick Off Vet Welcome: BSU/ Mecha Welcome N.S., no date- (Box-folder 44-35)
- Portraits: Pickett, John COB Senior Faculty Group Shot, Holtman/Wallace Softball Shot, Wellington Paws, 2008- (Box-folder 44-36)
- Portraits: Blaine bennet and Players; Corona, Rich; D'Aquisto, L.; Christian/Smart with Emmy; Holtfreter, Bob; Horsley, Jackson; housing Group Portraits: Hudleson, J; Watson, B., 2008-2009 (Box-folder 44-37)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Cabinet 2008, Cheer Squad, CWU Legislative Team; DeShields, R.; Dicarlo, L.; Jerilyn McIntyre with Higher Education Coordinating board Resolution, Johnson, k.; Mack R.; Orchesis Portraits; Powell, J.; Presidential Candidates: Rittereiser, S.; String Faculty: Ventrees, B.; Cross Country Team (Box-folder 44-38)
- Portraits: Burns, K.; Fudacz, Ryan; James Brooks Historical, Kurtz, Martha; Lewis, Scott, Li, Chenyang; Nelson, Josh; Owen, Bill; Retiree Portraits and Reception; reed, Sam; Theater Students "bump", Torrens, Kyle, 2008- (Box-folder 44-39)
- Battle in Seattle, Shots by Nate Slover Disc 1, 2008- (Box-folder 44-40)
- Battle in Seattle, Shots by Nate Slover Disc 2, 2008- (Box-folder 44-41)
- Central Connections: Bennet, Blaine' Dean Hall construction, Dick Elliot "Primal Op" Hansen, Karen Jones (Boeing), General Mattis, Bishop, Kitna; Koons, Christine; Kurtz, Martha; Lambert, Connie, 2008- (Box-folder 44-42)
- Omar Surkatty, 2009- (Box-folder 44-43)
- Selski Forier Classrooms, 2009- (Box-folder 44-44)
- Police Department Prints by Nate Slover, 2009- (Box-folder 44-45)
- Science Classes Diaz; Carnell, Johansen, 2009- (Box-folder 44-46)
- Orchestra Portrait, 2009- (Box-folder 44-47)
- Gary Heesacker Teaching, 2009- (Box-folder 44-48)
- Nimnicht, Gary Teaching, Gaudino Family Portrait, 2009- (Box-folder 44-49)
- Wellington with Students/Hats Disc 1, 2009- (Box-folder 44-50)
- Wellington with Students/Hats Disc 2, 2009- (Box-folder 44-51)
- Rafting, Owls, 2009- (Box-folder 44-52)
- Orchestra Musicians in Action/Tuxes, Move-In, 2009- (Box-folder 44-53)
- Portraits ASCWUBOD group and Individual portraits, Boddy, Debbie; covey, Terri; Darda, Dave Anatomy Class Shot; Dixon, Dan; Drummond, Scott; Estrada, E.; Jansen, J.; Karageorges, DeeAnn; Kaufman, Davis; Khullar, Shree; library Faculty, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 44-54)
- Barrett, Carmelita; Barrett, Carrie; Caravelli, t.; Fields, L.; Haystack, Adam; Moffet, Dave (in surplus/surplus historical items) Reardon, Kate, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 44-55)
- Portraits Abdallah, Laila; Ashbrooks, Steve; Denison, Christina; Lafluer, Lori; Linnell, Ginger; palmer, Shawn CWU Hummer; Scott, Eric; Turley, Christine Commencement, 2010- (Box-folder 44-56)
- Fall Portraits: Camp Group and Individual, UNHSP RA Groups, 2010- (Box-folder 44-57)
- Fall Portraits; ASCWUBOD Studio White; Bahr, Logan; brown, Terri; Champagne, Keith; Erickson, Ron; Eveslage, Beau; Rodgers, Forrest; Sargent, Erin; Shewey, Justin; Whiteside, Kelsey, 2010- (Box-folder 44-58)
- Portraits: Students with Hats on White Altman, Matt; Bryner, Stephanie; Callahan, Bret and Cari; Civic Engagement group Shot; Class of 1960; Cutright, Patricia; Depiro, Carla; Diaz, Anthony; Drinkwater, John; Fudge, Rachel, 2010- (Box-folder 44-59)
- Teaching/Classroom Robinson, Steve-Ceramics Class, 2010- (Box-folder 44-60)
- Eng, Jason Mount Stuart Classroom and Portrait; Montgomery, Aaron Math on Whiteboard and Portrait; Smart, Chris and Christian; Tom at Edit Station, 2010- (Box-folder 44-61)
- Distinguished professors: Erdman, Ruthi; Gries, Peter; Lonborg, Susan; Kern, Shirley; Kern; Shirley and James, Keith; Matayoshi, David; Melbourne, Tim; Turley, Kristine, 2010- (Box-folder 44-62)
- Events: C.O.B. Boardroom Meets Classroom, Outdoor Symposium, 2010- (Box-folder 44-63)
- Fall Portraits: CEC Pink Outfits Downtown, Chamber Choir, CTED 2010, Dickerson, Andre, Orchestra, Sterkel, Kendra Empmo (Box-folder 44-64)
- Spring Portraits: track Team Photo, AFROTC Barge portrait, Army ROTC Battalion, Brooks and Sykes with Rover, Distinguished Professors Altman/Easley/Holtfreter/Powell; Tosch, Bob, 2009- (Box-folder 44-65)
- Spring Portraits: Bleggi, Brett; Camp Staff: Diaz, Anthony with Phosphors, Gaudino, Jim and Katie Casual Jefferies, Steve; Mayer, Olga; Thompson, Kieth, 2009- (Box-folder 44-66)
- C.O.B. Economics 101: Young, M. class; Goodenberger, M.; percussion Class, 2009- (Box-folder 44-67)
- Miscellaneous Portraits: Aho, M.; Ames, E.; Anderson, L.; Appleton, L.; Bloxham, S.; Bottcher, M.; Breyfogle, S.; Bryan, Vince/Carol; Bryson, E.; Burroughs, Capt.;C.O.T.S. Deans: Garland,K.; Hull, M.;Ninneman, J.; Knirck, M.; Kroeger, A.; Palmer-Nutt, G.; University Police Group/Individuals: Rolfe, L.; Shanks, A.; Surkatty, O.; Swanson, T., 2009- (Box-folder 44-68)
- Fall Portraits: camp choir coaches COB Dean's Council CTED, 2009- (Box-folder 44-69)
- ROTC Award Ceremony, with Mike Gregoire, 03/2009 Vietnam Airlines Graduate, Nate Slover Photos (Box-folder 44-70)